（ギャモン）消えねえ。　違う…
俺とは…　パズルの重みが…。
He's totally different. He doesn't feel the weight of the puzzle.
カイト　てめえは　何だ…。
Dammit, Kaito, what are you trying to do to me?
俺に何をさせたいんだ…。
（ミハル）え～～っ？！
もう　こんな時間？！
Oh no, it's already time!
I'm gonna be late!
遅刻　遅刻！　あっ？！
お兄ちゃん…。
朝飯は　がっつり食べてけよ　ミハル。
Gammon?
You should eat a big breakfast, Miharu.
また　貧血を起こすぞ。
Your anemia might act up again.
ごめんね　お兄ちゃん。
朝ごはん　作らせちゃって。
Sorry, thanks for making breakfast.
Ah, that reminds me.
きのう「月刊パズルプリンス」の
編集さんから電話あったよ。
I got a call from the Monthly Puzzle Prince yesterday.
Your puzzle won this month's popularity award again, and by a wide margin!
お兄ちゃんのパズル
今月号も　読者投票ダントツ１位！
「次も　どうか　ひとつ」だってさ。
ウフフッ。
They're hoping to get a new one, you know.
友達に言いふらしたいなぁ！
I so want to tell all my friends...
今をときめく　売れっ子パズル作家
地堂　刹が→
...that the most influential, best-selling puzzle maker, Chido Setsu,
うちのお兄ちゃんだって。
感謝してます。
is actually my brother!
I'm really grateful.
こうして　きょうだい２人
生きていけるのも兄上あってこそ。
It's all thanks to you that just the two of us can live together like this.
早く食っちまえよ。
けど　すごいよね　お兄ちゃんは。
Just hurry up and eat.
But seriously, you're amazing, Gammon.
パズル解くのも　得意だけど
作るのは　もっと得意なんだもん。
Not only are you really good at solving puzzles, but you're even better at making them!
心の声
解くよりも…　作る方が…。
Better at making... than solving?
kimi no nounai he shinnyuu nemutteiru sukima ni
I infiltrate your brain while you're sleeping.
Baby, open the gate!
fukuzatsu sugi sekyuriti kakusareru to abakitaku naru
The security's too tough, but I want to expose what's hidden.
barabara ni chirabatteiru pasuwado wo hiroi atsume
I gather the pieces of the shattered password.
kakushin ni sematte iku sono shoutai wo misete
I get close to the core. Show me who you really are!
kantan ni kuria dekinai saki nante motto yomenai
I can't clear it easily. I can't even see what lies ahead.
kaidoku fukanou sumairu kikenna pazuru
Your indecipherable smile is a hazardous puzzle.
rokku sareta doa aru nara zutto tataite miru beki kazana hiraku wa
When you see a locked door, you should just hit it until a crack opens.
eien ni hodokenai nazo nanka wa nai
There's no mystery that lasts forever!
makiokosu, it's a supernova
I made it, it's a supernova!
tobikiri shigekitekina hirameki wo agemashou
Let's flash so bright it'd hurt!
Misskey-Misskey La-Tu-Ma
yume no naka it's a supernova
In my dreams, it's a supernova!
watashi wa sou brain diver
Yeah, I'm the brain diver!
kimi ga sagashi motometeru kotae ni nareru made
Until I can find the answer you're looking for...
Brain diver!
Treason Against the Light
（アイリ）天才テラスの雰囲気
なんか変ですね。
Something's weird about the Genius Terrace today.
Flutter-flutter.
カ・イ・ト・君。
Ka-i-to!
Flutter-flutter.
（武田）そりゃ変だろうさ。
あの格好じゃ。
Of course it's weird. Check out that outfit.
（相沢）何　考えてんすかね？
井藤のやつ。
Seriously, what is she thinking?
それも　ありますけど
いつもは　５人なのに　今日は…。
And that's only one problem.
There's usually the five of them, but today...
Don't tell me you're ignoring me when I'm dressed like this.
いや～～～！　ガン無視だよ　カイト。
この格好を目の前にして～。
まあ　無理ないけど。
Not that I'd be surprised.
And you know,
つ～かさ！　こういう時こその
カイトを励ます会じゃん！
this is a great time for another "Cheer up, Kaito!" party!
コスプレして集合って
あれほど言ったのに…。
I even told them to dress up as something,
どうして　みんな来ないわけ？！
so why haven't any of them shown up?!
何すんだよ！　ノノハ！
ああ　ハハハハッ　ごめん　ごめん。
What the hell, Nonoha?!
Sorry, my bad.
やっぱり考えちゃう？
ご両親のこと。
You were thinking about your parents, weren't you?
It must've been a shock.
ショックだよね。　まさか
おじさんと　おばさんが…。
To think they were...
けど　カイトは幸せだった。
But you were happy back then.
あのころの思い出
ニセモノじゃないから。
Those happy memories are real. They'll live on in your heart forever.
ずっと　カイトの中で
生き続けるんだから…。
分かってる。
I know.
俺が今　考えてたのは
ルークのことだ。
I was thinking about Rook.
ルーク君？
ああ　あいつも子供のとき
親と別れたって言ってた。
Rook?
Yeah. When we were kids, he told me that he was separated from his parents as well.
けど　俺と違って　独りぼっちで…。
But unlike me, he was alone... in that disgusting, creepy room.
あんな　クソおぞましい部屋で…。
鬼だぜ…。
Those POG bastards... are devils!
ＰＯＧは！
Even after what they put you through, you still worry about Rook.
ここまでされても　ルーク君のこと
心配するなんて…。
カイトは強いね。
You're really strong, Kaito.
バカだけど…。
おい！　バカは余計だ。　バカは！
But stupid too.
Skip the stupid part!
（校内放送・バロンの声）「大門カイト君
逆之上ギャモン君　キュービック・Ｇ君→
Daimon Kaito, Sakanoue Gammon,
Cubic Galois, Ana Gram, Ito Nonoha,
アナ・グラム君　井藤ノノハさん。
至急　学園長室へ来てください」。
please come to the principal's office immediately.
I repeat,
今の声　学園長だよ。
That's the principal's voice!
Daimon Kaito, Sakanoue Gammon,
あのタヌキ　無事だったのか！
行くぜ　ノノハ！
うん！
That old fox was okay!
Cubic Galois, Ana Gram, Ito Nonoha,
Let's go, Nonoha!
それ　着替えてけよ！
アホ　丸出しだぞ！
But you should change first! You look retarded!
please come to the principal's office immediately.
ちょっと！　今　それ言う！
…ってか　アホって！
Wait, now you're saying that?! And it's retarded?!
（ドアを開ける音）
おっさん！
Old man!
（バロンの声）「よく来たね　カイト君」。
（２人）だぁ～～～！
Thank you for coming, Kaito.
The hell is this?
何じゃ？　こりゃ。
（ソウジ）「私は　√学園　学園長の
解道バロン。→
I am principal of the Root Academy, Kaido Baron.
ちょっぴり　お茶目な魚座のＢ型」。
I'm a bit of a prankster, a Pisces, and my blood type's B.
軸川先輩…　それは？
Jikugawa, what is that?
「ボイスチェンジャー。　私に
もしもの事があったときは→
A voice changer. If by chance something were to happen to me,
Jikugawa is to use this to prevent chaos among the students.
生徒の混乱を防ぐために
軸川君が　私の影武者を…」。
それを君たちに伝えようと
思ってね。
I just wanted to tell you that.
それじゃあ　学園長は…。
いまだに行方不明…。
Then the principal...
...is still missing.
大丈夫。　あの人は　煮ても
焼いても食えない　規格外生物だ。
It's okay. He's a tough guy to deal with. He's off the charts.
必ず　無事でいるさ。
I'm sure he's fine.
そう…　そうだよな。
うん　そうだね。
Yeah... you're right.
Yeah, that's right.
まあ　その影武者も大変だけど。
Although acting as his double isn't easy.
心配すんな。　俺はＰＯＧなんかに
絶対　負けねえ。
Don't worry! I won't lose to the POG!
だよね。　みんなで力を合わせれば。
That's right! We'll all work together!
あれ？
そういえば　ギャモン君たちは？
Now that you mention it, where are the others?
そうそう。　３人とも　今日は
顔を見せないんですよ。
Oh, right. They haven't shown up today.
まるで　私たちを
敬遠してるみたい。
It's like they're avoiding us.
心の声
敬遠…　やはり　この時が…。
Avoiding... So that's how it is.
（エレナ）まあ　ジーニアスの　おじさま。
３問目で　もうギブですの？
Mr. Genius, are you already giving up on the third question?
エレナ　悲し～い。
I'm so sad!
Don't you dare make Elena sad!
（観客）
エレナちゃんを困らすんじゃねえ！
（奥寺）ううっ　ぐ～っ！
（観客）てめえ　パズル王だろうがよ！
Aren't you the Puzzle King?!
ふざけんな！
早く答えろ！
Hurry up!
Answer already!
お願い　おじさま　エレナに
ひどいこと　させないで！
Please, mister, don't do something that cruel to me!
そ　そんなこと言われても…。
Even if you say that...
ああ　こんなに　かわいいのに
エレナってば　なんて罪な女。
I thought I was cute, but I guess I'm actually just a bad girl.
あああ～。
ダメ～　泣いちゃダメ～！
No! Don't cry!
ご主人様方　こんな小悪魔なエレナを
許してポロリン！
My beloved masters, will you drop the charges against me?
We'll drop them!
（一同）許すポロリン！
ポロリン！
（倒れる音）
Drop?!
イャー！　エレナの勝ちポロリ～ン！　ウフフッ。
And with a drop, I win!
（エレナ）どういう風の吹き回し？
What got into you?
あんたが　私の番組
見に来るなんて。
You're the last person I'd expect to come watch my show.
キャラチェンジしたんだな　お前。
悪い？　女王様キャラもマンネリ。
You changed characters again, didn't you?
So what? The princess type doesn't work anymore.
生き馬の目を抜く芸能界じゃ
当然よ。
Show business is a dog-eat-dog world. It's normal.
ヘッ！　久しぶりに　そのむかつく
ドヤ顔　見たら　気が晴れたぜ。
Seeing your annoying face after such a long time has cheered me up.
なんか　妙ね。
You're weird.
あんた　悩んでない？
フン。
Is something troubling you?
Did I hit the mark?
図星？
うるせえよ。　じゃあな。
Shaddup! Bye.
待ちなさいよ！　パズル作家　地堂　刹。
Stop right there, puzzle maker, Chido Setsu!
お前…　どうして…。
How did you...
ＰＯＧの情報網を甘く見ないで。
Don't underestimate the POG's intel network.
たまに　いるのよね。　ギヴァーとソルヴァー
どっちの才能も持つ　両刀使いが。
There are many people like you.
People who have the talents of both a Giver and a Solver.
あんたの悩みって　それ系？
何が言いたい？
Is that what's troubling you?
What do you mean?
Would you like to get some tea, Genius Giver Chido?
お茶でもしない？
天才ギヴァーの地堂センセ。
キューちゃん！　どうして昼休み
来てくれなかったのよ！
Cubie, why didn't you come at lunch break?
とにかく出てきて。
Anyway, get out here! Or just open the door!
≫ドア　開けて　開けてよ！
（キュービック）
届かないよ…　カイトには…。
I can't reach Kaito.
絵を描くのに専念したい？
アナまで…。
You want to concentrate on painting?
You too...
なんか　２人とも変だよ。
Both of you are acting weird.
まるで　カイトと私を
避けてるみたい…。
It's like you're avoiding me and Kaito.
（アナ）アナが思うに　太陽は　月を
追いかけて　遠くへ行っちゃった。
I think... the sun has chased the moon very far away.
太陽って…　カイト？
The sun is... Kaito?
The path is too dark; I can't go with him.
道が暗くて
アナには　ついていけない。
アナ…。
Ana...
私は…　私は　ついていくよ。
I... I'm going with him!
どこまでも！
どんなに遠くなっても！
Forever and ever! No matter how far!
（ビショップ）ルーク様。
（ルーク）あっ！
Sir Rook.
少し　お疲れなのでは？
Are you tired?
僕が？　なぜだい？
いえ　別に…。
Me? Why would I be?
Never mind, I apologize.
報告を続けたまえ。
Continue your reports.
（メイズ）はい。
先般の作戦が　功を奏し→
Yes, sir.
The plan is starting to show results.
エジソンのキュービック・Ｇ
ダビンチのアナ・グラムは→
Cubic Galois the Edison and Ana Gram the Da Vinci
大門カイトから離れつつあります。
are becoming more distant from Daimon Kaito.
（ダイスマン）は～い！
じゃあ　次は　僕のパズルで。
Great! My puzzle is next.
ここで一気に　仲間やっちゃえば
大門カイトは　完璧　独りぼっちっす。
We'll take out all his friends, and then he'll be completely alone.
それは　どうかな？
Don't be so sure about that.
殺してしまったら
彼らは永遠になってしまう。→
If they die, they will stay with him forever.
生きていてこそ
カイトは孤独を深めるんだ。
If they are alive, it will only worsen Kaito's solitude.
う～！
そこが　よく分かんないっす。
I don't get it.
（フンガ）残るは２人。
井藤ノノハは問題外としても→
That leaves these two.
We can take Ito Nonoha for granted,
ガリレオの逆之上ギャモンが…。
but Sakanoue Gammon the Galileo...
（ルーク）いや　やっかいなのは彼女だ。
No, the girl is the most troublesome one.
彼女こそが　最も太い
カイトの精神的支柱。
She is the strongest pillar of mental support for Kaito.
It will be much easier to deal with Galileo.
むしろ　ガリレオ君の方が　たやすい。
（ビショップ）ルーク様の読みどおり
逆之上ギャモンは　今→
Just as Sir Rook says, it would definitely seem that Sakanoue Gammon is wavering.
大きく揺らいでいる様子です。
フッ…　僕には　彼の思いが
手に取るように分かるよ。
I can read his feelings like an open book.
（ギャモン）カイト！
心の声
てめえの返答しだいでは…。
Kaito! It all depends on your answer.
それ　一応　学園長なんだけど。
That's the principal, by the way.
で？　俺に話ってのは？
So, what did you want from me?
ここ数日で　状況は
劇的に悪化した…。
The situation has gotten much worse in the past few days.
学園長を失い
僕もＰＯＧに目をつけられ→
We lost the principal, and the POG is watching me, so my movements are restricted.
うかつには動けない。
ギャモン君　君は　これからどうする？
Gammon, what are you going to do?
さあな　俺も　悩み多き
お年ごろなんでね。
Who knows? I'm a troubled old man too.
小１時間考えてみるわ。
頼りにしてるよ。
I'll think about it an hour or two.
That would be great. Kaito is being isolated, just as the POG wants.
ＰＯＧの思惑どおり　カイト君は
孤立を深めてるからね。
ノノハは　ついていくぜ。
何が起ころうと　カイトに。
Nonoha will stay by his side, no matter what happens to him.
Nonoha?
ノノハ君？　ノノハ君は　別に…。
She's different.
ＰＯＧも　パズル能力のない彼女には
興味ないだろう。
The POG won't care about her since she's talentless when it comes to puzzles.
神のパズル…　神の書…。
The Divine Puzzle. The Divine Revelations.
ＰＯＧは　神のパズルを解き
神の書を手に入れるためなら→
The POG wants to solve the Divine Puzzle to get the Divine Revelations.
手段は選ばねえ。
ああ　そうだね。
They won't be picky about their means.
That's true.
金にも　糸目は
付けねえだろうしなぁ。
No price is too steep.
ノノハ…。
心の声
Nonoha...
どうか　したかい？
さ～て　夕飯　何にすっかな？
Is something wrong?
Hmm, what should I have for dinner?
ん？！　こっ　これは？！
Th-This is... such a high level, beautiful sudoku!
何という　高度で美しいナンプレ…。
これを　ギャモン君が…。
Gammon made this?
ギャモン君…　君は一体…。
Gammon, what on Earth...
そんなわけで
アナも　キューちゃんも…。
So now, Ana and Cubie have left too.
At this rate, Kaito will be alone.
このままじゃ　カイトは
独りぼっちになっちゃう。
だから　ギャモン君は
ずっと　カイトの友達でいて。
So please, stay Kaito's friend.
今までどおり　カイトと…。
Just like always, together...
Kaito? What are you doing here?
カイト？！　ど　どうして？！
なんだ？！　ノノハも一緒か。
Huh? You're here too, Nonoha?
俺が呼んだ。
えっ？！
I called him.
What's going on? What's this urgent business you were talking about?
何なんだよ？
改まって　俺に用って…。
二度と言わねえから　よく聞け。
I won't say it again, so listen up.
返答しだいでは
俺も腹をくくるぜ。
Depending on your answer, I'm prepared to do the worst.
カイト…　今後　一切ノノハに近づくな。
近づいたら　ガチで潰す！
Kaito.
Stay away from Nonoha.
If you won't, I'll crush you!
うっ！
ギャモン君！
Gammon!
はっ！　くっだらねえ！
何　言いだすかと思ったら…。
Ha! That's so lame!
To think I was worried about what you wanted.
バッカじゃねえのか　お前？　そんな事
お前に指図されるいわれは　ねぇ！
Are you stupid or what?
I don't recall ever having to take orders from you!
それが　お前の答えか？
だったら　どうした？
Is that your answer?
So what if it is?
カイト…　てめえと出会ってから
アナや　キュービックが　どうなった？
Kaito! What happened to Ana and Cubic after they met you?
どうなんだよ？！
そういうやつなんだよ　てめえは！
See?! That's the kind of guy you are!
仲間の事なんざ　考えられもしねえ
独りよがりのパズルバカ。
You're just a lonely little puzzle freak that doesn't give shit about his friends!
自分だけ　パズルと遊んでりゃ
ごきげんなガキなんだ！
You're just a brat who only cares about playing with puzzles!
ちょ　ちょっと　ギャモン君！
そこまで言わなくても…。
W-Wait, Gammon... You shouldn't...
ノノハ！　お前　カイトに殺されるぞ！
Nonoha!
Kaito's going to get you killed!
オルペウスの腕輪に飲まれたカイトは
我を失って　お前を見殺しにする。
Under control of the Armband of Orpheus, he'll sacrifice you without a thought!
カイトは　周りを不幸にする
疫病神なんだよ！
He's the angel of death to the happiness of people around him!
やっ…　疫病神？！
A-Angel of death?
だから　金輪際
カイトに関わるんじゃねえ！
So stay away from him, no matter what!
余計な　お世話よ。
I don't need your advice.
I decide what I do. And I'll do what I want.
私のことは　私が決める！
私の好きにする。
見損なったわ　ギャモン君！
（雷鳴）
I misjudged you, Gammon.
フッ　フフフフッ…　ああ　そうかい…。
これで決まりだ。
Oh really? Well, it's over now.
俺も　今後は
好きにさせてもらうわ。
I'll do what I want as well.
俺は　やっと分かったんだよ。
俺にとって　てめえが何なのかを。
I finally understand... what you are to me.
敵…　たたき潰すべき敵だ。
An enemy. An enemy I must crush.
大門カイト！　俺と戦え！
Daimon Kaito, fight me!
俺の作ったパズルに挑戦しろ！
ギャモン君！
Challenge the puzzle I made!
Gammon!
You guys are insane!
バッカじゃないの。　あんたら～！
What the...?
これは…。
心の声
本当に　ギャモンが　これを？
Did Gammon really build this?
Make a 'T' out
of the four pieces!!
Connect the 9 dots with
4 continuous lines!!
What numbers are A and B!?
He made those puzzles too.
あの時も　自作のパズルを？　お前！
You!
そうよ。　俺様は　ソルヴァーとしても
ギヴァーとしても　超一流。
That's right! I'm above first class as both a Solver and a Giver!
てめえなんざ　足元にも及ばねえ
真の天才なんだよ！
I'm a true genius! You can't even lick my feet!
寝言　言ってろ！
俺に解けないパズルは　ねえ！
Dream on! There's no puzzle I can't solve!
だから　何で　こうなるわけ？！
Why does it have to come down to this?!
マジで　２人とも　リアルバカ！
You two are seriously insane!
こいつは　対戦型パズルだ。
This is a duel-type puzzle.
ボールの数は　９×９の８１本。
The board is nine by nine, making eighty-one poles.
両端にあるのが
それぞれのマザーポールだ。
The mother poles are at our respective corners.
２つのポールをたたいて
間にレーザーの壁を作る。
If you hit two neighboring poles, a laser wall will form between them.
一度に作れる壁は　８つ。
Your circles can use a maximum of eight walls at a time.
まず　マザーポールを含めて
１つの輪になるように作り始める。
First, you build a circle around your mother pole.
輪にしなければ　消えちまう。
If they don't connect to form a circle, they disappear.
輪は　１人　１つしか作れねえが
大きくすることも→
You can only have one circle,
but you can make it bigger,
ぶった切って
小さくすることもできる。
or smaller by cutting parts off.
If we both turn on the same wall, it becomes double-layered.
双方が　同じポールを使って
壁を二重にすることもできる。
相手を　デッドエンドへ追い詰めて
四方を囲めば勝ちだ。
You win if you lock your opponent in at a dead end.
分かった。
I get it.
パズルタイムの始まりだ。
It's puzzle time.
いくぜ！　順番もクソもねえ！
早いもん勝ちだ！
Go! Nothing but speed matters here! The faster one wins!
Oh, really?!
ああ　そうかよ！
うそ？！　早い者勝ちじゃ
パズル作ったギャモン君の方が→
No way! If the faster one wins,
then Gammon has the advantage because he made the puzzle!
有利じゃない！
んなこた　ねえ！
Not if I can help it!
ヘッ！　甘えな！
あ～！
Too weak!
心の声
２人とも　本気で
戦ってる…　なんで？
They're both going all out.
Why?
おもしれえ！　いいパズルだぜ！
It's fun! This is a good puzzle!
ギャモン　お前　やっぱ　すげえな！
You're really amazing, Gammon!
へっ！　１つ　言い忘れていたぜ。
Oh, I forgot to mention one thing.
デッドエンドに追い詰められて
負けが決まれば…。　えいっ！
If you get stuck in a dead end and lose...
ばっ　爆発って　なんで？！
A bomb?! Why?!
I told you. It's a dead end!
言っただろ。　デッドエンドだってな！
Gammon!
ギャモン。
Stop this, Gammon!
やめろ　ギャモン。
こんな…　こんなパズルは！
This... This puzzle...
やめねえよ。
てめえを潰すまではな！
I won't stop.
Not until I've crushed you!
ギャモン！
へっ！
Gammon!
くたばれ　カイト！
この愚者のパズルで！
You're going down, Kaito! In my Fools' Puzzle!
何っ？！　愚者のパズルだと？！
What?! A Fools' Puzzle?!
そうよ。　こいつは　てめえのために
作ってやった愚者のパズルなんだよ！
Damn right! This is a Fools' Puzzle I made just for you!
えい！　どうした？！
ファイ・ブレインの最有力候補者！
What's wrong, mister "strongest Phi Brain candidate"?!
ビビって　腰が抜けたか！
You scared shitless?!
ギャモン…　てめえ…。
Gammon, you...
You're going down, Kaito.
くたばれ…　カイト…。
許さねえ。　お前のクソパズルは
俺が　たたき潰す！
You'll regret this. I'm going to smash your goddamn puzzle!
むなしい響きだぜ。
勝てると思うか！
Big words... You think you can win?!
ギュワッ！
えいっ。
腕輪を使えよ　カイト！
Come on, use the Armband, Kaito!
いつもみてえに　腕輪に頼れよ！
Rely on it like always you do!
うるせえ！
Shut up!
（２人）えいっ！
うっ。　あっ。　何？！
What?!
しまった！
あっ！
Dammit!
焦って　詰めを誤ったな。
け～っ。
You made a mistake in your rush.
刺せよ　とどめを！
じゃねえと　勝ちには　なんねえぞ。
Take the final strike!
It's not a victory if you don't.
腕輪に飲まれた　てめえにゃ
感情がねぇ！
You don't have emotions when you use the Armband!
やれるだろう？！
やれってんだよ！　おら～～っ！
If you can do it, then do it!
No, Kaito!
ダメ！　カイト～！
情けをかけたことを
必ず後悔させてやる。
You'll regret having mercy.
アインシュタインの…　大門カイト。
Einstein... Daimon Kaito.
あっ…　ギャモン君！
Gammon!
どうして…　こんなことに…。
Why did it have to come to this?
カイト！
Kaito?
うっ　カイト…。
Kaito...
うわ～っ！　やっぱ　私の料理って
最終破壊兵器…。
My cooking is like a weapon of mass destruction.
おなか　すいたよ～。
早く帰ってきてよ　お兄ちゃ～ん！
I'm hungry! Hurry up, Gammon!
（エレナ）
本当に　あいつと　やったんだ。
You really fought him.
驚いたわ。　ちょっとした事件ね。
I'm surprised. This is a fairly big development.
本当に　いいの？　後悔しない？
Are you really okay with this? You won't regret it?
したことねえよ…　後悔なんざ。
I never regret anything.
大門カイトを潰すため
俺は　ＰＯＧのギヴァーになる。
To defeat Daimon Kaito, I...
...will become a Giver of the POG.
tsukue no ue de umareta sekai
This world born on my table.
ichiban saki ni kimi ni misetakatta
I wanted you to see it first.
karappo no heya sotto nukedashite hashiri hajimeteta
I sneaked out of the empty room and started to run.
iki hazamasete oka wo noboru to
As I got to the top of the hill, out of breath,
kimi ga saki ni tsuite matteita ne
you were already there waiting for me.
takusan no hajimete kimi to mitsuketa takaramono datta
It was the first of many treasures we would find together.
kanashisa de afureta toki wa
When sorrow was overflowing in me,
nanimo iwazu ni tada soba ni ite kureta ne
you just silently stayed by my side.
ima de mo wasurenai yo
I still haven't forgotten that.
mata aou ne yakusoku wo shiyou
Let's promise we'll meet again.
kie wa shinai ano hi no sayonara
The goodbye of that day we'll never forget.
boku no subete kimi ga kureta michi
All I have I got from you,
zutto kokoro no naka hikaru yo
and it will all shine in my heart forever.